Railway Labor Executives' Association Additional Records 5728
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
- Series XIII: Office Files, 1982
  - Railway Labor Executives Association: Washington Job Protection Agreement Cases, 1984 (Box 55, Folder 43)
    Filings before the Section 13 Committee.
  - Railway Labor Executives Association: Committees (General), 1984 (Box 55, Folder 44)
  - Railway Labor Executives Association: Committee on Legislation and Safety, 1984 (Box 55, Folder 45)
    Testimony and correspondence in re the need for federally mandated and enforced safety standards for railroads.
  - Railway Labor Executives Association: Executives Committee, 1984 (Box 55, Folder 46)
  - Railway Labor Executives Association: Labor Management Task Force on Terminals, 1984 (Box 55, Folder 47)
  - Railway Labor Executives Association: Immigration Problems, 1984 (Box 55, Folder 48)
  - Railway Labor Executives Association: Subcommittee on Alcoholism and Drug Abuse, 1984 (Box 55, Folder 49)
  - Railway Labor Executives Association: Northeast Illinois Railroad Corporation Labor/Management Committee, 1984 (Box 55, Folder 50)
    Agendas and minutes of meetings
  - Railway Labor Executives Association: Committee on Railroad Retirement, 1984 (Box 55, Folder 51)
  - Railway Labor Executives Association: Committee on Railway Labor Act, 1984 (Box 55, Folder 52)
  - Railway Labor Executives Association: Committee on National Transportation Policy, Mergers, Consolidation, and Passenger Service, 1984 (Box 55, Folder 53)
  - Railway Labor Executives Association: Legislative Representatives, 1984 (Box 55, Folder 54)
  - Railway Labor Executives Association: Director of Governmental Affairs Legislative Report, 1984 (Box 55, Folder 55)
  - Railway Labor Executives Association: Prospective Employees (General), 1984 (Box 55, Folder 56)
  - Railway Labor Executives Association: Financial Statements, 1984 (Box 55, Folder 57)
  - Railway Labor Executives Association: Lawyers (General), 1984 (Box 55, Folder 58)
  - Railway Labor Executives Association: Lawyer Bills [folder 1 of 3], 1984 (Box 55, Folder 59a)
  - Railway Labor Executives Association: Lawyer Bills [folder 2 of 3], 1984 (Box 55, Folder 59b)
  - Railway Labor Executives Association: Lawyer Bills [folder 3 of 3], 1984 (Box 55, Folder 59c)
  - Railway Labor Executives Association: United States Court of Appeals (District of Columbia) Number 84-1048 - Railway Labor Executives Association versus United States Railroad Retirement Board, 1984 (Box 55, Folder 60)
    Brief of Amicus Curiae from the Government of Canada in Support of the RLEA. April 16, 1984.
  - Railway Labor Executives Association: Strikes (General), 1984 (Box 55, Folder 61)
  - Railway Labor Executives Association: Press Releases, 1984 (Box 55, Folder 62)
  - Railroads: General, 1984 (Box 55, Folder 63)
  - Railroads: Association of American Railroads (AAR), 1984 (Box 55, Folder 64)
  - Railroads: National Railway Labor Conference (NLRC), 1984 (Box 55, Folder 65)
  - Railroads: Hospital Associations (General), 1984 (Box 55, Folder 66)
  - Other Organizations: American Federation of Labor-Congress of Industrial Organizations (AFL-CIO), 1984 (Box 55, Folder 67)
  - Other Organizations: Committee on Political Education, 1984 (Box 55, Folder 68)
  - Other Organizations: Legislative Council, 1984 (Box 55, Folder 69)
  - Other Organizations: Executive Council, 1984 (Box 55, Folder 70)
  - Other Organizations: Miscellaneous and General, 1984 (Box 55, Folder 71)
  - Other Organizations: National Safety Council, 1984 (Box 55, Folder 72)
  - Other Organizations: National Association of Retired and Veteran Railway Employees, 1984 (Box 55, Folder 73)
  - Other Organizations: Labor Bureau - Gus Homer [folder 1 of 2], 1984 (Box 55, Folder 74a)
    Correspondence and filings in re ICC Docket No. 37025
  - Other Organizations: Labor Bureau - Gus Homer [folder 2 of 2], 1984 (Box 55, Folder 74b)
  - Other Organizations: LABOR Newspaper, 1984 (Box 55, Folder 75)
    Financial reports, annual report, and minutes of meeting of Board of Directors.
  - Other Organizations: Special Election Year Editions of LABOR Newspaper, 1984 (Box 55, Folder 76)
  - Other Organizations: National Association of Railroad Passengers (NARP), 1984 (Box 55, Folder 77)
  - International Affairs (General), 1984 (Box 55, Folder 78)
  - International Affairs: Bureau of International Labor Affairs - Foreign Visitors, 1984 (Box 55, Folder 79)
  - Commuter Problems: General, 1984 (Box 55, Folder 80)
  - Government: Purchase of Conrail - Conrail Case 2 and Case 3, Financial Summary and Projections, 1984 (Box 56, Folder 1)
  - Government: Purchase of Conrail - Morgan Stanley Financial Assessment, June 1984 (Box 56, Folder 2)
  - Government: Purchase of Conrail - Metromedia Inc. Stockholder Meeting Invitation and Business Offers, 1984 (Box 56, Folder 3)
  - Government: Purchase of Conrail - Conrail Labor Agreement and Proposed Sale, 1984 (Box 56, Folder 4)
  - Government: Purchase of Conrail - Proposed Conrail Agreement, 1984 (Box 56, Folder 5)
  - Government: Purchase of Conrail - Conrail Task Force Meeting, 1984 (Box 56, Folder 6)
    Agendas and minutes of meetings.
  - Government: Purchase of Conrail - Proposed Tentative Conrail Agreement, 1984 (Box 56, Folder 7)
  - Government: Purchase of Conrail - Base Case 1 Analysis, 1984 (Box 56, Folder 8)
  - Government: Purchase of Conrail - Conrail Task Force and News Articles About Conrail Sale, 1984 (Box 56, Folder 9)
  - Government: Purchase of Conrail - Base Case 2 Analysis, 1984 (Box 56, Folder 10)
  - Government: Purchase of Conrail - Proposed Plan for the Disposition of Conrail, 1984 (Box 56, Folder 11)
  - Government: Purchase of Conrail - United States District Court (District of Columbia), Railway Labor Executives' Association v. Consolidated Rail Corporation, 1984 (Box 56, Folder 12)
    FOIA case.
- Series XV: Desk and Reader Files, 1975-1985
  - Desk File, October-December 1975 (Box 56, Folder 13)
  - Desk File, January-March 1976 (Box 56, Folder 14)
  - Desk File, April-June 1976 (Box 56, Folder 15)
  - Desk File, July-September 1976 [folder 1 of 2] (Box 56, Folder 16a)
  - Desk File, July-September 1976 [folder 2 of 2] (Box 56, Folder 16b)
  - Desk File, October-December 1976 [folder 1 of 2] (Box 56, Folder 17a)
  - Desk File, October-December 1976 [folder 2 of 2] (Box 56, Folder 17b)
  - Desk File, January-March 1977 [folder 1 of 3] (Box 56, Folder 18a)
  - Desk File, January-March 1977 [folder 2 of 3] (Box 56, Folder 18b)
  - Desk File, January-March 1977 [folder 3 of 3] (Box 56, Folder 18c)
  - Desk File, April-June 1977 [folder 1 of 2] (Box 56, Folder 19a)
  - Desk File, April-June 1977 [folder 2 of 2] (Box 56, Folder 19b)
  - Desk File, July-September 1977 (Box 56, Folder 20)
  - Desk File, October-December 1977 (Box 56, Folder 21)
  - Desk File, January-March 1978 [folder 1 of 2] (Box 57, Folder 1a)
  - Desk File, January-March 1978 [folder 2 of 2] (Box 57, Folder 1b)
  - Desk File, April-June 1978 (Box 57, Folder 2)
  - Desk File, July-September 1978 (Box 57, Folder 3)
  - Desk File, October-December 1978 (Box 57, Folder 4)
  - Desk File, January-March 1979 (Box 57, Folder 5)
  - Desk File, April-June 1979 (Box 57, Folder 6)
  - Desk File, July-September 1979 (Box 57, Folder 7)
  - Desk File, October-December 1979 (Box 57, Folder 8)
  - Desk File, January-March 1980 (Box 57, Folder 9)
  - Desk File, April-June 1980 (Box 57, Folder 10)
  - Desk File, July-September 1980 (Box 57, Folder 11)
  - Desk File, October-December 1980 (Box 57, Folder 12)
  - Desk File, July-September 1981 [folder 1 of 3] (Box 57, Folder 13a)
  - Desk File, July-September 1981 [folder 2 of 3] (Box 57, Folder 13b)
  - Desk File, July-September 1981 [folder 3 of 3] (Box 57, Folder 13c)
  - Desk File, October-December 1981 [folder 1 of 3] (Box 57, Folder 14a)
  - Desk File, October-December 1981 [folder 2 of 3] (Box 57, Folder 14b)
  - Desk File, October-December 1981 [folder 3 of 3] (Box 57, Folder 14c)
  - Desk File, January-March 1982 [folder 1 of 4] (Box 57, Folder 15a)
  - Desk File, January-March 1982 [folder 2 of 4] (Box 57, Folder 15b)
  - Desk File, January-March 1982 [folder 3 of 4] (Box 57, Folder 15c)
  - Desk File, January-March 1982 [folder 4 of 4] (Box 57, Folder 15d)
  - Desk File, April-June 1982 [folder 1 of 2] (Box 57, Folder 16a)
  - Desk File, April-June 1982 [folder 2 of 2] (Box 57, Folder 16b)
  - Desk File, July-September 1982 [folder 1 of 2] (Box 57, Folder 17a)
  - Desk File, July-September 1982 [folder 2 of 2] (Box 57, Folder 17b)
  - Desk File, October-December 1982 [folder 1 of 2] (Box 58, Folder 1a)
  - Desk File, October-December 1982 [folder 2 of 2] (Box 58, Folder 1b)
  - Desk File, January-March 1983 (Box 58, Folder 2)
  - Desk File, April-June 1983 [folder 1 of 2] (Box 58, Folder 3a)
  - Desk File, April-June 1983 [folder 2 of 2] (Box 58, Folder 3b)
  - Desk File, July-September 1983 [folder 1 of 2] (Box 58, Folder 4a)
  - Desk File, July-September 1983 [folder 2 of 2] (Box 58, Folder 4b)
  - Desk File, October-December 1983 (Box 58, Folder 5)
  - Legislative Reader File [folder 1 of 2], 1983 (Box 58, Folder 6a)
    Carbon file of outgoing correspondence of the legislative committee.
  - Legislative Reader File [folder 2 of 2], 1983 (Box 58, Folder 6b)
  - Desk File, January-March 1984 [folder 1 of 2] (Box 58, Folder 7a)
  - Desk File, January-March 1984 [folder 2 of 2] (Box 58, Folder 7b)
  - Desk File, April-June 1984 (Box 58, Folder 8)
  - Desk File, July-September 1984 (Box 58, Folder 9)
  - Desk File, October-December 1984 (Box 58, Folder 10)
  - CONRAIL Reader File, January-March 1984 (Box 58, Folder 11)
    Carbon file of outgoing correspondence of the Conrail Task Force.
  - CONRAIL Reader File, April-June 1984 [folder 1 of 2] (Box 58, Folder 12a)
  - CONRAIL Reader File, April-June 1984 [folder 2 of 2] (Box 58, Folder 12b)
  - CONRAIL Reader File, July-September 1984 (Box 58, Folder 13)
  - CONRAIL Reader File, October-December 1984 (Box 58, Folder 14)
  - CONRAIL Reader File, January-March 1985 (Box 58, Folder 15)
  - CONRAIL Reader File, January-March 1985 (Box 58, Folder 16)